Presenter: Question one. How many UK episodes were there of the TV quiz
Who Wants to be a Millionaire? Is it a) sixty-six, b) six hundred and sixty-six,
or c) six thousand, six hundred and sixty-six?
Contestant: The answer is…six hundred and sixty-six.
There were six hundred and sixty-six UK episodes of the
TV quiz Who Wants to be a Millionaire?
Presenter: Question two. How many pubs in the UK have a quiz night?
Is it a) two hundred, b) two thousand, or c) twenty thousand?
Contestant: The answer is…twenty thousand.
Twenty thousand pubs in the UK have a quiz night.
Presenter: Question three. What is the most money in dollars
won by One person on TV quiz shows?
Is it a) five million, two hundred and twenty-three thousand, four hundred and fourteen,
b) fifteen million, two hundred and twenty-three thousand, four hundred and fourteen,
or c) fifty million, two hundred and twenty-three thousand, four hundred and fourteen?
Contestant: The answer is…five million, two hundred and twenty-three thousand, four hundred and fourteen.
The most money won by one person on TV quiz shows is five million,
two hundred and twenty-three thousand, four hundred and fourteen dollars.